You provide the fire
I'll provide the sacrifice
Lift your hands, Church!
You provide the Spirit
I will open up inside
You provide the fire
I'll provide the sacrifice
You provide the Spirit
I will open up inside
Fill me up God
Fill me up
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I need You to fill me up God
Fill me up
Anybody wants the Lord to fill them
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
You provide the fire
Lift your hands in worship
I'll provide the sacrifice
You provide the Spirit
I will open up inside
You provide the fire
I'll provide the sacrifice
You provide the Spirit
I will open up inside
Fill me up God
Fill me up
Somebody scream!
Fill me up God
Fill me up
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Are you ready to make a declaration?
Are you ready, Church? Let me see your hands up. Come on!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Hallelujah!
Come on, Choir!
You provide...
You'll provide the fire
I'll provide the sacrifice
I am believing in sacrifice to you Jesus
You provide the Spirit
I will open up inside
One more time.
If You provide the fire, Lord...
You provide the fire
I'll provide the sacrifice
Jesus! If You provide the Spirit...
You provide the Spirit
I will open up inside
Fill me up God
Fill me up
Somebody shout Jesus!
Jesus fill me up!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Worship Him!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Fill me up 'til I overflow
I wanna run over
Somebody scream!
I need you to fill me up
Fill me up
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
Fill me up
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Fill me up Lord
Fill me up
Hallelujah
Fill me up, come on!
Fill me up 'til I overflow
I wanna run over
I really love You, Jesus.
Fill me up 'til I overflow
I wanna run over
Fill me up.
Hallelujah!
Fill me up
Fill me up Lord
Fill me up God
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Fill me up Lord
Fill me up
Fill me up God
I wanna run over
The SCOAN Sunday Servirce
Fill me up 'til I overflow
I wanna run over
Put your hands together for Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Thank you!
Good Morning, Church!
Good Morning!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
If God is with us, no one can be against us.
Thank you.
You may be seated.
Thank you!
Wow!
If God is with you, no one can be against you.
If God is with me, no one can be against me
I salute you.
Amen!
Viewers at home, if God is with you, no one can be against you.
We salute your faith.
Good morning.
Hallelujah!
Amen.
Ah! Yes! I think you give me some of your time
before you set up the table for the stomach.
Because I know you have done a lot, you have wrestled with...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
How do you feel, if I just remain silent and quiet,
looking at your face and you are looking at my face?
What will be going on in your heart?
No, no, I will be silent for a while.
You too, I do not know what you will choose to do.
But I want to remain silent, looking at you, looking everywhere.
Tell me how you will feel!
Do you actually enjoy it if I remain silent, looking at you?
No!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Wow.
Do you mean it?
Yes!
I just say, let me give you some time to think about all these exercises you have done today,
and the testimonies you have received today too - you need time to think about them.
Ah...
Viewers at home, I know you are trying to remove your plates, arrange the table...
OK! Hallelujah!
Amen!
So today, we shall talk about some very simple issues but they are not simple.
The challenges we are facing today - we put ourselves where we are not
when it comes to things of the Spirit.
If there is any "simplest" Bible than the one we have, I would have asked you to be reading it.
It is like this Bible seems to be a bit difficult for you to understand,
because we twist everything; everything about God, we twist it.
God has no tongue but our tongue to tell you that what you are doing is wrong.
It is all about this issue of faith.
I realize that we base our spiritual experiences on feelings and emotions.
We do not know the difference.
Our spiritual experiences - we base them on feelings and emotions.
Today, this is what I am saying.
These are the challenges we are having all over the world today.
So many churches, prayer houses, you hear the noise of people every day,
but it is like Heaven does not know or hear.
- Are you with me?
- Yes!
People are men of prayer but perhaps not of faith.
Tell your neighbor.
I cannot hear you!
People are men of prayer perhaps not of faith.
In Jesus' name, in Jesus' name...!
They are men of prayer but perhaps not of faith.
This means, we are saying words, not praying prayer.
You know, there is a difference between saying words and praying prayer.
When you base your spiritual experiences on feelings and emotions,
you will find yourself saying words not praying prayer.
Today, people base their spiritual experiences on feelings and emotions.
And we all know that feelings are influenced by what we see, hear, read,
what our circumstances look like.
Overflow Congregation
Many are not here today because their vehicle's engine knocked.
And who gave to them that vehicle?
Many are not here today because they have some assignment, meeting.
They need to attend the meeting and they have to avoid coming here.
And God is ONLY, not one of those things.
The SCOAN Service
You are here today because there is no serious commitment.
Today is a free day; there is no serious commitment, no job, nothing...
You cannot just be sitting at home that is why you are here.
And serious things too can take you out of here, if you receive a phone call concerning your business,
and you learn that that business is "click",
you need to receive millions today - you have to walk out of the church.
Problems arise when feelings and emotions change.
The SCOAN Sundays Service
Let's take a look at the Book of John 13:34 as our proof text.
"A new commandment I give you: Love one another."
Listen to that!
"A new commandment I give you: Love one another.
As I have loved you, so you must love one another.
By this everyone will know that you are my disciples, if you love one another."
It means in this case, the Lord is saying: "Love your neighbour",
and your neighbour can be your enemy,
can be someone who does not share the same faith with you.
He says: "Love them".
Overflow Congregation
How will you love them without faith?
Our faith must be stable, must be consistent.
For faith to be stable and consistent, it must be based on something with more stability
than our feelings, than our emotions.
The Word of God - the same yesterday, today and forever and it will continue to be the same.
Jesus is the same yesterday, today and forever.
You are not saved because you feel you are saved.
You are saved because you have put your faith in God's Word and acted on it.
When you act on the Word, you bring Jesus on the scene instantly.
Whatever we are doing today, without acting on the Word, we cannot bring Jesus on the scene.
We continue to shout and shout, "Ah!"
To realise this, the Word must prevail in our lives.
You cannot be known as a child of God, as born again unless the Word prevails in your life.
This is what the Bible says here:
"By this every one will know that you are my disciples if you love one another".
You cannot be known as a child of God unless the Word of God prevails.
For now you are carnal because you are ruled by the senses.
Because you are ruled by feelings, by emotions,
you are carnal and to be carnally minded is death.
Remember, as a child of God, you are a spirit.
Listen to your spirit and obey it;
your spirit is controlled by the Holy Spirit.
But the life we live today, the so called Christian is carnal.
It has not happened until it happens to you,
until you see, until you touch, until you hear.
When others are giving testimony, you say, "Until I give my own testimony, I will not believe."
When others are giving thanks to God, shouting, "Hallelujah!",
you are trying to see what happens before you can say, "Hallelujah".
Many of us are here today to see by yourselves.
Our circumstances dictate the direction to follow.
When there is money here, we say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
When there is no money, "Jesus, be cursed!"
When there is food on the table, we say, "Hallelujah!"
But when there is no food on the table, "Let Jesus be cursed!"
This is life depending on senses and feelings.
You hear noise of prayer everywhere; prayer houses...
People are praying but perhaps not of faith,
and only faith pleases God.
Only faith hears God.
Only faith reaches God.
In 1 Corinthians 3:3...
When the Word has not prevailed, we walk in poverty,
and our testimony is only of needs and lack.
When the Word prevails in our lives, we use the knowledge that is given to us in the Word.
Do not forget, it is the Word that taught us the value of the name, Jesus.
It is the Word that taught us the authority of the name, Jesus
and our legal right to use the name, Jesus.
When the Word prevails in your life, you have what God says you have,
you can do what God says you can do and you are what God says you are.
The question you need to ask yourself is, "Am I a child of God?"
Because the Bible says, you will never be known as a child of God
if the Word has not prevailed in your life.
Acting on the Word brings Jesus on the scene.
Are you a child of God?
That is a question you need to ask yourself.
Am I a child of God?
Question for you to answer.
Ask your neighbour, "Are you a child of God?"
Are you a child of God?
That is the question for you to answer.
I will not ask you; you will answer it on your own.
Am I a child of God?
Are you praying prayer or are you saying words?
FAITH IS NOT A FEELING
These two; which I believe today, 90% of Christians all over the world are saying words not praying prayer.
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Are you one of the 90%?
You go to the mountain to pray and fast; praying, praying, praying.
Ask your neighbour, "Are you saying words or praying prayer?"
I cannot hear you!
Are you saying words or are you praying prayer?
If you are saying words, each time you are saying words not praying prayer - attack.
Don't forget the seven sons of Sceva.
They said, ''In Jesus' name!''
It is like honey.
Wherever you drop honey, insects seek.
Insects.
When you say, "Jesus!", satan and his demons, "Who is calling the name?"
It is like a tiger here.
You will see how you will begin to run.
They begin to run, "Who is calling the name? By what authority are you calling that name?"
By the time they know, you have no authority, you have no legal right to call the name "Jesus", they attack you.
These are the attacks many of you receive today.
You say, "Jesus!"
"Eh,eh,eh - that name! Who is calling? Who is calling?"
They want to know who is calling.
They will now look - "By what authority?"
And they realise that you are saying words, not praying prayer.
They attack you.
Different attacks you are having today.
You say you pray - attack.
You pray - nightmare, because you are not praying, you are saying words.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When that name is pronounced, if the Word prevails in your life, it will show in your posture.
We can see it in your voice, if you are truly born again.
When you talk, one will know this is a born again.
Your posture, your dominion...
A born again, when a born again is going...
When you see the dominion, when you see the born again, you will know.
Many of you look around, just look around - this one is just fat, just tall, just good appearance -
he is empty for satan.
In your posture, one can see if you are born again, one can see it in your voice.
Your dominion, your countenance: "Ah, this is a born again."
You will see it clearly.
Satan just looks:
- Jesus!
- Hm! This voice is not of a born again.
That is how they got the seven sons of Sceva.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You can see it in his posture, in his dominion, in his appearance, in his voice, when a born again talks.
Jesus - power; power - Jesus.
Born again - power; power - born again.
Christian - power; power - Christian. That is it!
He moves - power; long turn with power; look with power;
the voice - power; the posture - power; dominion...
I just have to bring you back to what you have underestimated, belittle.
The message is for little children, but you are very very little, you are a kindergarden before God,
because of the things of the spirit.
I have no power of my own
Holy Spirit I look upon You
Help me
I have no power of my own
Right now, begin to pray the character of the Holy Spirit into your life.
Pray the character of the Holy Spirit into your life.
Right now, while you are sitting down, begin...
Open your lips.
Pray the character of the Holy Spirit into your life.
Be the Spirit of adoption to me, Holy Spirit!
Rise up!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Oh, how I love Jesus!
Open your lips; begin to pray the character of the Holy Ghost.
Pray the character of the Holy Ghost into your life.
Oh, how I love Jesus
Because He first loved me
Pray the character of the Holy Ghost into your life!
Be the Spirit of adoption to me!
Oh how I love Jesus
Because He first loved me.
Begin to pray the character of the Holy Ghost into your life.
Be the Spirit of adoption to me in the name of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Amen!
- I cannot hear your voice!
- Amen!
Ask your neighbour: "Where are you?"
Because some of you are not here.
Are you here?
- You, you are here?
- Yes!
We shall know; let us continue!
If you are not here, let us invite you in.
I say you have two natures in one person - you and your divine.
- Hallelujah!
- Amen!
As a Christian, you are not human, you are a spirit.
You listen to your spirit, obey your spirit because your spirit is under the control of the Holy Ghost.
Hallelujah
Remain quiet.
Allow yourself...
Your heart is the contact point; your heart is the prayer room.
Where is your heart?
Mean it.
Whatever you say, mean it!
Hallelujah
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Right now, ask Him to give you faith to believe.
You want Him to give you faith to believe.
Give me faith, Lord, to believe.
Not "I believe, help my unbelief".
Give me faith to believe.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
- In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
- Amen!
Every anxiety, depression, downcast,
worry about now and your future...
Out!
You know that cannot happen in the presence of God.
When you stand before Him and you begin to worry about now and the future - this is torture of satan.
That is the way satan tortures people.
You begin to worry.
With Him all things are possible: Why should you begin to worry about now and your future?
Leave it for Him; do not worry yourself!
You need a free spirit now; you want to be free, you want to leave it for Him.
With Him all things are possible.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank You, Lord!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Amen!
- I cannot hear you!
- Amen!
- You mean it?
Thank You, Lord!
You may be seated, thank you.
Because many "Amen" can come by senses, by feelings...
Because you hear people saying, "Amen", you say, "Amen".
That is feeling, that are just senses we are talking about.
"Ah! The man said I should say 'Amen', I have to say 'Amen'."
That is not from your heart.
This is why I ask you if you mean it,
or you hear people say "Amen", you say, "Amen".
you see people sitting down, you sit down,
when I say "Rise up for prayer", you rise up - not that you really mean to rise up.
You must mean it.
Whatever you do must come from your heart.
Our heart is the contact point of the Holy Ghost.
You must not go by majority but by God's authority.
When I say, "Rise up for prayer" and you know your spirit does not agree, you sit down.
When I say "Amen" or "In Jesus' name" and you know your spirit does not agree, don't say "Amen".
- In Jesus' name!
- Amen.
- I cannot hear you.
- Amen!
Thank you.
Viewers at home, thank you wherever you are, whatever you are doing now, I know you are with us.
Hallelujah!
I know, you are with us.
Viewers, I know you are with us!
Distance is not a barrier; you just need God's faith to believe.
We shall believe that by now, you are there.
- Hallelujah!
- Amen.
Above all powers
Above all kings
Above all nature
And all created things
Above all wisdom
And all the ways of men
You were here
Before the world began
Above all kingdoms
Above all thrones
Above all wonders
The world has ever known
Above all wealth
And treasures of the earth
There's no way
To measure what You're worth
Crucified
Laid behind a stone
You lived to die
Rejected and alone
Like a rose
Trampled on the ground
You took the fall
And thought of me above all
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT Esther Mwelwa
RV ROBERT BEGIER 20/07/2018 + Mel